<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2016-09-07T10:57:32.835-07:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="wmyersta"
        cq:template="/apps/beagle/templates/freelinkpage"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Source Serif Readme"
        sling:resourceType="beagle/components/freelinkpage"
        bodyClass="whiteBackground"
        browserTitle=" Source Serif Pro Readme file"
        languageDirection="ltr"
        pageTitle="Source Serif Pro Readme file">
        <contentbody
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="beagle/components/parsys">
            <text_3_95f9ab95-80c6-4fed-bd9d-b228b78e4960
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="beagle/components/text"
                text="&lt;p style=&quot;font-family: tahoma, arial, helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px;&quot;>This document contains product information, updates, and troubleshooting tips.&lt;/p>&#xa;"/>
            <text_5ed2294d-e9cd-4df1-86e7-68fb45f030c3
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="beagle/components/text"
                text="&lt;p>&lt;strong>History&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;https://typekit.com/fonts/source-serif-pro&quot;>Source Serif Pro&lt;/a> is a serif typeface in the transitional style, designed to complement &lt;a href=&quot;https://typekit.com/fonts/source-sans-pro&quot;>Source Sans&lt;/a>. Their close companionship is achieved by a careful match of letter proportions and typographic color. While designed to harmonize with its serif-less counterpart, Source Serif often takes its own direction, in part because the two are inspired by different historical precedents. Source Serif is loosely based on the work of Pierre Simon Fournier, and many idiosyncrasies typical to Fournier’s designs (like the bottom serif on the b or the middle serif on the w) are also found in Source Serif. Without being a pure historical revival, Source Serif takes cues from the Fournier model and reworks it for a modern age.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Source Sans and Source Serif also have different personalities because they spring from the hands of different designers. Source Serif was designed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/products/type/font-designers/frank-griesshammer.html&quot;>Frank Grießhammer&lt;/a>, Source Sans was designed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/products/type/font-designers/paul-hunt.html&quot;>Paul Hunt&lt;/a>. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/products/type/font-designers/robert-slimbach.html&quot;>Robert Slimbach&lt;/a> consulted on both designs, which helped maintain the overall family harmony. Either design feels confident on its own but also works in combination with the other — just like their designers do.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Source Serif continues Adobe’s line of high-quality open source typefaces. Designed for a digital environment, the letter shapes are simplified and highly readable. Its historical roots, combined with the guidance through an experienced designer give the typeface a strong character of its own that will shine when used for extended text on paper or on screen.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>There is still more to come for Source Serif. Additional weights, Italic cuts, and Cyrillic and Greek language support are all planned. If you are interested in contributing to this open source project, please visit this &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/adobe-fonts/source-serif-pro&quot;>project page&lt;/a> for information on how to become involved. Source Serif Pro can be adapted and redistributed according to the terms of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://wwwimages.adobe.com/content/dam/Adobe/en/products/type/pdfs/eulas/open-font-license.pdf&quot;>Open Font License (OFL) agreement&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;strong>Menu Names And Style Linking&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In many Windows&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup> applications, instead of every font appearing on the menu, fonts are grouped into style-linked sets, and only the name of the base style font for a set is shown in the menu. The italic and the bold weight fonts of the set (if any) are not shown in the font menu, but can still be accessed by selecting the base style font, and then using the italic and bold style buttons. In this family, such programs will show only the following base style font names in the menu:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;table cellpadding=&quot;1&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;>&#xa;&lt;tbody>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Black&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro ExtraLight&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Light&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Semibold&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;/tbody>&lt;/table>&#xa;&lt;table cellpadding=&quot;1&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;>&#xa;&lt;tbody>&lt;tr>&lt;th>Menu Name&lt;/th>&#xa;&lt;th>plus Style Option&lt;/th>&#xa;&lt;th>selects this font&lt;/th>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>[none]&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Regular&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Bold&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Bold&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Black&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>[none]&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Black&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro ExtraLight&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>[none]&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro ExtraLight&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Light&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>[none]&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Light&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Semibold&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>[none]&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;td>Source Serif Pro Semibold&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;/tbody>&lt;/table>&#xa;&lt;p>On the Mac OS operating system, although each font appears as a separate entry on the font menu, users may also select fonts by means of style links. Selecting a base style font and then using the style links (as described above for Windows applications) enhances cross-platform document compatibility with many applications, such as Microsoft Word, although it is unnecessary with more sophisticated Adobe applications such as recent versions of Illustrator, Photoshop&amp;nbsp;or InDesign&amp;nbsp;software.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>One should not, however, select a base font which has no style-linked variant, and then use the bold or italic styling button. Doing so will either have no effect, or result in programmatic bolding or slanting of the base font, which will usually produce inferior screen and print results.&lt;/p>&#xa;"/>
            <text_0_dcab923f-25a0-4b3e-9696-7d4f75d69402
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="beagle/components/text"
                text="&lt;p>For all fonts of family Source Serif Pro: version 1.017 created on Tue Sep 16 17:12:36 2014.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>version 1.017 created 2014/09/16&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Added three more weights: Black, Light, ExtraLight.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Added missing L/lcommaaccent (U+013B/C) to all fonts.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>version 1.014 created 2014/04/27&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>First release.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;"/>
            <text_1_7667dd3d-68c1-4485-be39-296c05ed11fe
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="beagle/components/text"
                text="&lt;p>Some glyphs in the font cannot be accessed unless you are using an OpenType compatible application.&lt;/p>&#xa;"/>
            <text_2_08b3eb3d-145f-4337-97d5-8c3fd6fecf30
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="beagle/components/text"
                text="&lt;p>If you require technical assistance, please email us at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:type-questions@adobe.com&quot;>type-questions@adobe.com&lt;/a>. Font specific resources can also be found on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://forums.adobe.com/community/typography_fonts&quot;>Adobe Type user-to-user forums&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"/>
        </contentbody>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
