<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2018-01-18T16:06:44.749Z"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="spopescu"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-08-17T16:10:35.117Z"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="wmyersta"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/beagle/templates/searchpage"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Search"
        jcr:uuid="6bc65aa2-631c-405a-8abe-9361332da594"
        sling:resourceType="beagle/components/searchpage"
        alignment="left"
        allContent="All content"
        appliesTo="Applies to:"
        apply="Apply"
        backToTop="Back to top"
        breadcrumbSearch="Search"
        browserTitle="Search"
        clearFilters="Clear filters"
        didYouMean="Did you mean"
        duration="Duration:"
        enablekeymatchservice="true"
        enterSearchTerms="Please enter one or more search terms in the search box above."
        filter="Filter"
        globalnavHighlight="Auto-detect"
        globalnavProfileTheme="default"
        groupSectionNavItems="no"
        hideInBreadcrumb="true"
        keymatchserviceprovider="aem"
        metaDescription="Search"
        mostRecent="Most recent"
        mostRelevant="Most relevant"
        next="Next"
        noResults="Your search of Entire Site for &lt;strong>{{searchTerm}}&lt;/strong> did not match any documents. Use these &lt;a href=&quot;#search-tips&quot;>search tips&lt;/a> to help you find what you're looking for."
        noResultsTips="&lt;ul>&lt;li>Make sure all words are spelled correctly.&lt;/li> &lt;li>Use quotes to search for an entire phrase, such as &quot;creative suite master collection&quot;&quot;.&lt;/li>&lt;li>Try some of these &lt;a href=&quot;#search-tips&quot;>search tips&lt;/a>.&lt;/li> &lt;/ul>"
        page="Page"
        placeholder="Search Adobe.com"
        previous="Prev"
        product="Product"
        productLookup="Product lookup"
        result="result"
        results="results"
        resultsFor="results for"
        searchInsteadFor="Search instead for"
        searchResults="Search results"
        searchserviceprovider="uss"
        searchTips="&lt;h3>Search Tips&lt;/h3>&lt;br>&lt;h4>Use quotation marks&lt;/span>&lt;/h4>&lt;p>Use quotation marks to find words that must appear adjacent to each other, such as &lt;em>transparent background&lt;/em>. Without quotes, the search results will include the words &lt;em>transparent&lt;/em> and &lt;em>background&lt;/em>, but not necessarily in that order (i.e., the words may appearanywhere, in any order, within the document). &lt;/p>&lt;br>&lt;h4>Use plus (+) or minus (-)&lt;/h4>&lt;p>Use a plus sign when your search term or phrase must appear in the search results. Use aminus sign to indicate undesirable term(s). The plus sign tells the search engine that acertain word or phrase is required in the search results, and a minus sign indicates that aword or phrase must be absent in the search results.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Note: A phrase must be contained within quotation marks. Leave no spaces between theplus or minus sign and the term.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Example: &lt;em>+photoshop -elements &lt;/em>will return only documents that contain the word&lt;em>photoshop&lt;/em> and do not contain the word &lt;em>elements&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>&lt;br>&lt;h4>Use field searches&lt;/h4>&lt;p>Field searches allow you to create searches for words that appear in a specific part of a document. A field search can be performed on body text (&lt;em>body:&lt;/em>), title text (&lt;em>title:&lt;/em>), description (&lt;em>desc:&lt;/em>), keywords (&lt;em>keys:&lt;/em>), or URL (&lt;em>url:&lt;/em>). The field name should be inlower-case and immediately followed by a colon. There should be no spaces between thecolon and the search term.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Note: The field searches can only be followed by a word or phrase. Phrases must becontained within quotation marks.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Examples:&lt;br>&lt;em>title:&quot;reader download&quot;&lt;br>desc:red-eye&lt;br>keys:acrobat&lt;br>body:muse&lt;br>url:adobe.com/products/&lt;/em>&lt;/p>&lt;br>&lt;h4>Use wildcards&lt;/h4>&lt;p>Wildcard searches can expand the number of matches for a particular request. The *character is used as the wildcard character.&lt;/p>&lt;p>For instance, searching for &lt;em>licens*&lt;/em> will find the words &lt;em>license, licensing,&lt;/em> and &lt;em>licenses&lt;/em>. Searching for &lt;em>*graph&lt;/em> will find the words &lt;em>photograph, paragraph,&lt;/em> and anyother word that ends with &lt;em>graph&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Wildcards may be combined with the standard plus (+) and minus (-) modifiers, quotes forphrases, and field search specifiers.&lt;/p>&lt;p>Examples:&lt;br>&lt;em>convert* pdf&lt;br>media encod*&lt;/em>&lt;/p>"
        selectAll="Select All"
        serverDown="We're sorry, we are unable to perform a search right now, please try again later."
        showAllResultFor="Showing {{resultsCount}} results for"
        showingResultsFor="Showing results for"
        supportCommunity="Support &amp; Community"
        title="Adobe.com"
        useH1Tags="[pageTitle,pageTitle]">
        <sectionMore jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
